blackovis.com 2019-06-15

# Privacy Policy

#### Your Personal Information

Wondering where the personal information you put into our site will end up? Let's cut to the chase. We will not share or sell your personal information with an outside party. Your information will be used to place and maintain your orders and for our crew to contact you with questions about your order or to give information about items on our site or our latest hunting deals. We take our responsibility seriously to keep your information private and secure. 

We collect your name, shipping and billing address, credit card number, e-mail address and phone number when you place an order. However, **we do not store credit card information on our servers**. After you place an order, your credit card info pertaining to the transaction is held in a separate, secure location. 

#### Opt Out

If you have chosen to receive personalized messages, newsletters, or promotional communications, you can cancel this at any time by emailing us to let us know that you wish to be taken off of the lists. 

#### Cookies

We use cookies on our site, which you can reject, but this may slow down BlackOvis's ability to personalize things like your cart and your account. Enabling cookies is certainly up to you. 

#### Questions?

If you've got any questions about our privacy policy, want to remove your information from our database, have a picture of your latest kill to send us, or you just want to talk hunting, drop us a line at [customerservice@blackovis.com](mailto:customerservice@BlackOvis.com).
